(Sheldon:)for why you think
you sell shoes and yogurt.
(Penny:)Okay, you know what?
(Penny:)Let's just try
a different improv. Uh..
(Penny:)Oh, this time
we will be two winos
(Penny:)living under a freeway overpass.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and we're going
to use props?
(Penny:)You bet.
(Penny:)I had dreams,
you know.
(Penny:)I was gonna be famous.
(Penny:)Show everybody back home
I could be someone.
(Penny:)Now look at me.
(Penny:)Want some?
(Sheldon:)You have any frozen yogurt?
(Leonard:)I'm still not adjusted
(Leonard:)to how the SyFy channel
spells their name now.
(Leonard:)S-y-F-y.
That's "siffy."
(Raj:)Uh-huh.
(Leonard(phone rings):)Hello?
(Leonard(phone rings):)Oh, my God! Is he okay?
(Raj:)What happened?
Hang on. Hang on.
(Raj:)Uh-huh.
(Leonard:)Okay, thank you.
(Leonard:)Howard was on his scooter,
and got hit by a truck.